
    let antonyms=[
        {
            question:'ENORMOUS',
            op1:'Soft',
            op2:'Average',
            op3:'Tiny',
            op4:'Weak',
            answer: 'Answer: Option C',
            exp:`Explanation:

            No answer description available for this question.`,
        },
        {
            question:'ARTIFICIAL',
            op1:'Red',
            op2:'Natural',
            op3:'Truthful',
            op4:'Solid',
            answer: 'Answer: Option B',
            exp: `Explanation:

            No answer description available for this question.`
            //exp:'',
        },
        {
            question:'EXPAND',
            op1:'Convert',
            op2:'Condense',
            op3:'Congest',
            op4:'Conclude',
            answer: 'Answer: Option B',
            exp: `Explanation:

            No answer description available for this question.`
        },
        {
            question:'MORTAL',
            op1:'Divine',
            op2:'Immortal',
            op3:'Spiritual',
            op4:'Eternal',
            answer: 'Answer: Option B',
            exp: `Explanation:

            No answer description available for this question.`,
            //exp:'',
        },
        {
            question:'OBEYING',
            op1:'Ordering',
            op2:'Following',
            op3:'Refusing',
            op4:'Contradicting',
            answer: 'Answer: Option A',
            exp:`Explanation:

            No answer description available for this question.`,
        },
        {
            question:'BUSY',
            op1:'Occupied',
            op2:'Engrossed',
            op3:'Relaxed',
            op4:'Engaged',
            answer: 'Answer: Option C',
            exp: `Explanation:

            No answer description available for this question.`
            //exp:'',
        }
       
    ]


    
    let syntonyms=[
        {
            question:'BRIEF',
            op1:'Limited',
            op2:'Small',
            op3:'Little',
            op4:'Short',
            answer: 'Answer: Option D',
            exp: `Explanation:

            No answer description available for this question.`,
        },
        {
            question:'AUGUST',
            op1:'Common',
            op2:'Ridiculous',
            op3:'Dignified',
            op4:'Petty',
            answer: 'Answer: Option C',
            exp: `Explanation:

            No answer description available for this question.`
        },
        {
            question:'ALERT',
            op1:'Energetic',
            op2:'Observant',
            op3:'Observant',
            op4:'Watchful',
            answer: 'Answer: Option D',
            exp: `Explanation:

            No answer description available for this question`
        },
        {
            question:'WARRIOR',
            op1:'Soldier',
            op2:'Sailor',
            op3:'Pirate',
            op4:'Spy',
            answer: 'Answer: Option A',
            exp: `Explanation:

            No answer description available for this question. `,

        
        },
        {
            question:'FAKE',
            op1:'Original',
            op2:'Imitation',
            op3:'Trustworthy',
            op4:'Loyal',
            answer: 'Answer: Option B',
            exp: `Explanation:

            No answer description available for this question`,
        }
    ]


